# **Artur Babichev**

Mobile Developer

#### **PROFILE**

With **over 6 years of experience** in developing Android applications primarily using **Kotlin**, I am skilled in creating mobile applications from scratch and diving into existing codebases.

I have a strong background in writing and publishing libraries and setting up CI/CD processes.

Currently, I specialize in **Kotlin Multiplatform** development.

### **SKILLS**

Languages: Kotlin, Java

**Technologies/Tools**: Kotlin Multiplatform, Compose Multiplatform, Android SDK, Ktor/Retrofit, SQLDelight/Room, Koin/Dagger, JUnit/Mockito/Espresso, LeakCanary, Crashlytics, Gradle, Git, Fastlane, Docker, Github Action, Gitlab CI

## **EXPERIENCE**

Kotlin Multiplatform Developer, Pet-project; Ekaterinburg — Apr 2017 - Present Creating a pet project to enhance my skills.

*Technologies/Tools*: Kotlin Multiplatform, Compose, Coroutines, SQLDelight, Cipher, Koin, LeakCanary, JUnit, Espresso, Fastlane, Github Action.

Android Developer, Haiku.dev; St. Petersburg, Remote — Mar 2022 - Dec 2022 *Project*: **Edutoria.ru** - educational marketplace, team of 6.

Technologies/Tools: Kotlin Multiplatform, Compose, Coroutines, Dagger, Ktor.

Mobile Developer, Koshelek.ru; St. Petersburg, Remote — Aug 2021 - Nov 2021 *Project*: **koshelek.ru** - crypto wallet & P2P, team of 3.

*Technologies/Tools*: Kotlin Multiplatform, Compose, Coroutines, SQLDelight, Ktor.

Android Developer, Motorsport Network; Ekaterinburg — Jul 2018 - Aug 2021 *Project*: **Motorsport.tv** - client for video service. Application for AndroidTV (also for Amazon FireTV) and mobile. Team of 3.

*Technologies/Tools*: Kotlin, Leanback, ExoPlayer, Koin, RxJava, Glide, Timber, Retrofit, OkHttp, jUnit, Mockito, Docker, Gitlab Cl.

Android Developer, DataKrat; Ekaterinburg, Russia — Sep 2016 - Sep 2018 *Project*: BARS B2C - apps for scalable ticketing service, team of 2.

*Technologies/Tools*: Java, Kotlin, Dagger, RxJava, Realm, Picasso, Timber, Retrofit, OkHttp, jUnit, Mockito, Git.

## **EDUCATION**

Ural Federal University — Specialist Degree in Energy Industry, 2014

Tbilisi, Georgia artik222012@gmail.com